Guide to the Thomas Collier Platt Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1851-[1915?]; Series I; 3' (8 boxes)
  - Copies of Letters Sent to Benjamin Harrison (1881-1889)
    - Letters of congratulation to Benjamin Harrison recommending Platt for Secretary of the Treasury, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Letters of congratulation to Benjamin Harrison recommending Platt for Secretary of the Treasury, 1889 January (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Letters of congratulation to Benjamin Harrison recommending Platt for Secretary of the Treasury, 1889 February (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - Letters of congratulation to Benjamin Harrison recommending Platt for Secretary of the Treasury, undated (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Index to names of those who wrote Harrison recommending Platt for Secretary of the Treasury, undated (Box 7, Folder 163)
- Bills, Testimony and Speeches, Series II
  - United States Senate Bill 5006-promotion and restoration to status of Naval and Marine Corps officers lost through the war with Spain, 1898 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - New York Senate bills relating to the "removal of dead animals, night soil and offal", 1900 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - New York Assembly bill establishing a special committee to investigate "the proper boundaries of the State Park", undated (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - "An act to create and establish a uniform system for cities throughout the state [of New York]", 1901 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - Proposed amendment to the New York State Tax Law of 1899 (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - Statement by G. T. Rogers at the hearings on the Ford Franchise Tax Bill, 1899 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Proceedings of the New York Legislative Insurance Investigating Committee, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Testimony before the Committee on Printing relating to the completion and publication of "The Messages and Papers of the Presidents", 1900 (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - "Public Documents of the Early Congresses," by A. W. Greely, 1897 (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Five speeches of Thomas C. Platt, 1904 December 21, undated (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - "Dedication of the Soldier's Monument at Owego, New York, July 4, 1891." Address given by Thomas C. Platt (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Message from the President of the United States on a treaty with Cuba concerning the extradition of fugitives from justice, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 175)
- Biographical and Miscellaneous Material, Series III
  - Manuscript - "Which is the true Platt?", Circa 1909 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Photograph of Roscoe Conkling (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Excerpt from answer of emended complaint: William Barnes, Plaintiff-Appellant, against Theodore Roosevelt, Defendant, Respondent, [1915] (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Newspaper articles (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Lists of New York Assembly Republican District leaders (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Typescript relating events surrounding nomination of Roosevelt for Governor in 1898 (2 copies), Circa1902 May (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - "The Oracle." Issued by the Adelphi Society of Williston Seminary, 1877 April (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Scrapbook of mounted newspaper clippings relating to Senator Thomas C. Platt (1891-1910), Vol. 1 (Box 9)
  - Scrapbook of mounted newspaper clippings relating to Senator Thomas C. Platt (1891-1910), Vol. 2 (Box 10)
  - Scrapbook of mounted newspaper clippings relating to Senator Thomas C. Platt (1891-1910), Vol. 3 (Box 11)
  - Scrapbook of mounted newspaper clippings relating to Senator Thomas C. Platt (1891-1910), Vol. 4 (Box 12)
  - Scrapbook of mounted newspaper clippings relating to Senator Thomas C. Platt (1891-1910), Vol. 5 (Box 13)
- Additional Material, 1883-1898; Accession 2018-M-0011
  - Personal letter books, 1883-1898 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    Scope and Contents
    Two bound letterpress volumes of outgoing correspondence relating to the business, personal, and political life of Thomas Collier Platt (1833-1910). Includes typescript and handwritten letters, and an alphabetical numbered index of recipients in the front of each book.